<resources>

    <string name="description_eula">"<![CDATA[This Program Usage License Agreement (EULA) is a legal agreement between you (as an individual or a legal entity) and Technodynamite as the copyright holder of the Smart Home Controller, which includes software (programs) and supporting media such as boxes, good manuals print or online, hereinafter referred to as "SOFTWARE". By installing (installing on a Smartphone / Android Device), duplicating, or anything intended to use the SOFTWARE, you are willing to agree to and be bound by the clauses contained in this EULA. If you do not agree with or agree to the clauses contained in this EULA, cancel the SOFTWARE reservation before your payment is made. \n \nSOFTWARE LICENSE \nThis SOFTWARE is protected by law. Ownership of the SOFTWARE remains with the creator and you only have the right to use it. \n \n1. PERMISSION OF USE \nThis EULA grants you rights in the form of: \n \nSoftware \n- You are allowed to install SOFTWARE (install software into Smartphones / Android Devices) on multiple Smartphones as needed. \n- SOFTWARE can only be installed (installed into a Smartphone / Android Device) under the direction of Technodynamite's Technical Support. \n \nStorage Media \nYou are allowed to save copies of the original from the SOFTWARE solid disc on other storage media only to make a backup to anticipate possible damage to the original solid disc or CD. \n \n2. DESCRIPTION OF COPYRIGHT AND OTHER LIMITATIONS \nProhibition to Disassemble, Modify, and Engineer \nYou are not allowed to disassemble, modify, or engineer this SOFTWARE for any purpose or purpose. If there is an error in the SOFTWARE, please contact us to get the repair build (if available) and never make any changes or repairs yourself. \n \nProgram Technical Limitations \nTechnodynamite as the developer of the SOFTWARE does not act exclusively on the users of SOFTWARE so that if there are some things that are lacking about the SOFTWARE concerned, the user has no right to sue or force Technodynamite to make and / or correct the desired features, but the user has the right to submit suggestions and ideas for Technodynamite as the maker and developer of SOFTWARE unless there is an agreement. \n \nComponent Separation \nUsage rights of the SOFTWARE in one integrated unit. You are not allowed to use some of the components available for other purposes. \n \nRental / Rental. \nYou are not allowed to rent / rent and commercialize this SOFTWARE. \n \nReturn \nFor any condition you have no right to return (do return / refund) SOFTWARE that you have purchased and paid for. \n \nUnilateral Termination \nThe developer of Smart Home Controller in this case Technodynamite has the right to cancel this EULA unilaterally and legally if you are proven to violate the clauses contained in this EULA. \n \n3. COPYRIGHT \nAll equipment contained in the SOFTWARE, both manuscripts, drawings, and others are copyrighted by Technodynamite which is an integral part of the SOFTWARE. \n \n4. GUARANTEE \nYou are guaranteed to get a good product. If an error occurs or damage caused by an error in manufacture, you will get a repair build from the SOFTWARE free of charge if available. \n \n5. MISCELLANEOUS \nTechnodynamite has the right to change this EULA without prior notice. Other clauses that are included separately in the SOFTWARE can complement this EULA.]]>"</string>

</resources>
