<resources>

    <string name="description_eula">"<![CDATA[This Program Usage License Agreement (EULA) is a legal agreement between you (as an individual or a legal entity) with PT Smart IoT Devices as the copyright holder of the IoT Box Controller, which includes software, hardware, supporting media such as boxes, printed and online guidebooks, which is then abbreviated as "SMARTHOME DEVICES". By installing on a Smartphone/Android Device, duplicating, or anything intended to use the SMARTHOME DEVICES, you are willing to agree to and be bound by the clauses contained in this EULA. If you do not agree to the clauses contained in this EULA, cancel the SMARTHOME DEVICES reservation before your payment is made. \n \nSOFTWARE LICENSE \nThis SMARTHOME DEVICES is protected by law. Ownership of the SMARTHOME DEVICES remains with the creator and you only have the right to use it. \n \n1. PERMISSION OF USE \nThis EULA grants you rights in the form of: \n \nSoftware \n- You are allowed to install this application/software on multiple Smartphones as needed. \n- SMARTHOME DEVICES can only be installed (installed into a Smartphone/Android Device) under the direction of Technical Support. \n \nStorage Media \nYou are allowed to save copies of the original from the solid disc on other storage media only to make a backup to anticipate possible damage to the original solid disc or CD. \n \n2. DESCRIPTION OF COPYRIGHT AND OTHER LIMITATIONS \nProhibition to Disassemble, Modify, and Engineer \nYou are not allowed to disassemble, modify, or engineer this SMARTHOME DEVICES for any purpose or purpose, unless this activity is carried out in an effort to ensure the presence or absence of malware, spyware, viruses, etc. that are embedded in our products, on condition that you have received approval from us. If there is an error in the SMARTHOME DEVICES, please contact us to get the repair build (if available) and never make any changes or repairs yourself. \n \nProgram Technical Limitations \nPT Smart IoT Devices as the developer of the SMARTHOME DEVICES does not act exclusively on the users of SMARTHOME DEVICES so that if there are some things that are lacking with the SMARTHOME DEVICES, the user has no right to sue or force PT Smart IoT Devices to make or correct the desired features (unless there is an agreement), but the user has the right to submit suggestions and ideas for PT Smart IoT Devices as the maker and developer of SMARTHOME DEVICES. \n \nComponent Separation \nUsage rights of the SMARTHOME DEVICES in one integrated unit. You are not allowed to use some of the components available for other purposes. \n \nRent. \nYou are not allowed to rent and commercialize the SMARTHOME DEVICES. \n \nReturn \nFor any condition you have no right to return (do return/refund) SMARTHOME DEVICES that you have purchased and paid for. \n \nUnilateral Termination \nThe developer of IoT Box Controller in this case PT Smart IoT Devices has the right to cancel this EULA unilaterally and legally if you are proven to violate the clauses contained in this EULA. \n \n3. COPYRIGHT \nAll equipment contained in the SMARTHOME DEVICES, both manuscripts, drawings, and others are copyrighted by PT Smart IoT Devices which is an integral part of the SMARTHOME DEVICES. \n \n4. GUARANTEE \nYou are guaranteed to get a good product. If an error occurs or damage caused by an error in manufacture, you will get a build repair or product replacement according to the conditions stated on the warranty card. \n \n5. MISCELLANEOUS \nPT Smart IoT Devices has the right to change this EULA without prior notice. Other clauses that are included separately in the SMARTHOME DEVICES can complement this EULA.]]>"</string>

</resources>
